USS Arizona Collection, 1907-2015 (bulk 1915-1941)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 5: USS Arizona Reunion Association, Crew-Kin and Related Materials, 1960-2007
  - Subseries 4: Correspondence, 1984-2006
    This subseries is arranged chronologically and contains correspondence regarding administrative operations of the USS Arizona Reunion Association including the status of members, correspondence with media outlets, and other subjects pertaining to the USS Arizona and the USS Arizona Memorial in Pearl Harbor, Hawaii.
    - USS Arizona Superstructure, 1992-1995 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - General USS Arizona Reunion Association, 1984-2006 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Lenny Dorf Expulsion (1 of 2), 1985-1992 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Lenny Dorf Expulsion (2 of 2), 1985-1992 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona Memorial Cremains Plaque, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Allen Garth Ishman Expulsion, 1988-1992 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence on USS Arizona Reunion Association Stationary, 1988-2002 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - California State War Casualties, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - KGUN 9 News Story, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Ted Love Funeral, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      Folder contains obituary, funeral program and prayer.
    - University of Arizona Student Union Donations, 1989, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Orval A. Rosenbery Commemorative Medal, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - James Edward Everett Murder, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      James Everett was a chief of the USS Ellet who was murdered by Aaron Gust Taylor, MATTLC.
    - Navy-Marine Corps Relief Society, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - 50th Anniversary of Attack Plaque, 1992-1994 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day, 1992-1995 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      Folder contains information about House Joint Resolution no. 131.
    - Associated Press, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - USS Arizona Band, 1992-1994 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Enlisted Men Transfer, 1994-1996 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      Folder contains correspondence regarding the transfer of Leo Devere Amundson, Laverne Alfred Austin, A. Gildoin, Richard Eugene Gill, Donald Joseph Kusie, John David Miller, C.M. Parson to the USS Arizona.
    - Alfred Rosenthal Query, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Steve Matt Marnich, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Clinton Westbrook Plaque Proposal, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Hermosa Beach Port Call, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 23)
      Folder contains copies of emails.
    - Rare Pearl Harbor Attack Photos, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 5: Objects, 1971
    This subseries contains three dimensional commemorative objects collected by the USS Arizona Reunion Association.
    - 30th Anniversary of Attack on Pearl Harbor Bourbon Bottle, 1971 (Box 56, Item 1)
  - Subseries 6: Audiovisual Materials, 1934-1994
    This subseries contains audiovisual materials on VHS cassettes that provide historical accounts of the ship, Anniversary ceremonies, and USS Arizona Reunion Association reunion ceremonies.
    - America’s Defense Monitor, VHS Videocassette, 2 hours 2 minutes (Box 57, Item 1)
    - December 7: The Day of Infamy, 9 minutes; News 15 Story, 23 minutes; Russell McCurdy Speech, 39 minutes; Heroes, 49 minutes, VHS Videocassette (Box 57, Item 2)
    - Ensign Carl Alfred Weeden, VHS Videocassette, 59 minutes (Box 57, Item 3)
    - Here Comes the Navy, 87 minutes, 1934; San Diego Training Center, The USS Arizona and the Macon, VHS Videocassette (Box 57, Item 4)
    - Japanese News Story about Pearl Harbor, VHS Videocassette, 21 minutes (Box 57, Item 5)
    - Miscellaneous Footage, 47 minutes; CNN Pearl Harbor 50 Years After, 12 minutes, VHS Videocassette (Box 57, Item 6)
    - The Original USS Arizona Memorial Flagpole Dedication Ceremonies, VHS Videocassette, 1 hour 20 minutes, 1995 (Box 57, Item 7)
    - Paul Faulkner Interviews, VHS Videocassette, 33 minutes (Box 57, Item 8)
    - Pearl Harbor 50th Anniversary Filmed by Budd Nease, VHS Videocassette, 31 minutes, 1991 December 7 (Box 57, Item 9)
    - Pearl Harbor 50th Anniversary at USS Arizona Memorial, VHS Videocassette, 1 hour 10 minutes, 1991 (Box 57, Item 10)
    - Remember Pearl Harbor, Continental Airlines In-Flight Video Magazine, VHS Videocassette, 1991 (Box 57, Item 11)
    - Remember Pearl Harbor, Continental Airlines In-Flight Video Magazine, VHS Videocassette, 1992 January-February (Box 57, Item 11)
    - Remember Pearl Harbor with General H. Norman Schwarzkopf, Co-Hosted by Charles Kuralt, VHS Videocassette, 96 minutes (Box 57, Item 12)
    - Save Our History: USS Arizona, VHS Videocassette, 46 minutes (Box 57, Item 13)
    - Target: Pearl Harbor, The Special Commemorative Edition 1941-1991,VHS Videocassette (Box 57, Item 14)
    - USS Arizona Segment from Big Jim McLain, VHS Videocassette (Box 57, Item 15)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association in Tucson, AZ Taped by Howard Gasmann,VHS Videocassette, Approximately 5 Hours, 1988 (Box 57, Item 16)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Reunion and Auction, VHS Videocassette, 124 minutes, 1989 (Box 57, Item 17)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Visit to Titan Missile Museum, Airborne Museum and Banquet, VHS Videocassette, 82 minutes, 1989 (Box 57, Item 18)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Reunion Filmed by Howard Gasmann, VHS Videocassette, 235 minutes, 1990 (Box 57, Item 19)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Reunion, VHS Videocassette, 330 minutes, 1994 (Box 57, Item 20)
  - Subseries 7: Lauren F. Bruner Materials, 2013-2015
    This subseries contains materials relating to Lauren F. Bruner, a sailor on the USS Arizona who survived the Japanese attack at Pearl Harbor, December 7, 1941. Subseries contains materials documenting his visit to the University of Arizona on 2013 December 5 as well as commemorative apparel donated by Lauren F. Bruner.
    - Ephemera from Visit to the University of Arizona, 2013 December 5 (Box 58, Item 1)
    - USS Arizona Sketchbook Shirt, Blue, 2015 (Box 58, Item 2)
    - USS Arizona Sketchbook Shirt, White, 2015 (Box 58, Item 3)
    - US Navy, 12-7-41 Hat Signed by Lauren F. Bruner, undated (Box 58, Item 4)
    - December 7, 1941 T-Shirt, Grey, undated (Box 58, Item 5)
    - December 7, 1941 T-Shirt, Tan, undated (Box 58, Item 6)
    - USS Arizona BB-39 T-Shirt, Blue, undated (Box 58, Item 7)
    - USS Arizona BB-39 T-Shirt, Dark Blue, undated (Box 58, Item 8)
- Series 6: Appendices
  This series contains a binder that hold access copies of documents and photographic materials held in the collection.
  - Appendix C, U